-Kite is still alive.
-[gasps]
He would never be beaten,
not by something like that.
So now, we get strong and we find him.
[singer singing in Japanese]
[singer singing in English]
PROMISE X AND X REUNION
they must fulfill the one condition
set by Chairman Netero,
the leader of the Extermination Team.
What are those, Killua?
They're shogi tiles.
You take a piece of marked wood
and split it,
then you give each half
to a different person.
You can use it as proof of identity,
or to verify a document.
[Netero] We have already placed
two assassins in the nearest city.
each of the two assassins
have the other halves.
[indistinct conversations]
It's been erased.
That means someone checked the board.
[Gon grunts]
You must be Killua and Gon.
It's nice to meet you.
My name is Palm.
Let's sit down and have some tea.
I am Knov's pupil, you see.
He told me I would only get in his way,
but I insisted on accompanying him.
Who's that?
Don't know.
One of the guys with Chairman Netero?
[Palm] Yes, the one in a black suit.
My teacher is a wonderful man.
Cool and intelligent and composed.
[laughs]
I mean, respect is considerable factor
when it comes to falling in love,
after all.
[gasps] And my teacher knows nothing
about this, of course.
I have never said a word to him,
and I never will.
[slurping]
[both groaning]
[sighs]
Though in matters of the heart,
you can never really say for certain.
Love is a spontaneous thing
that goes without saying, don't you agree?
Uh, can I interrupt?
-Aren't we supposed to fight you?
-Huh?
Oh, dear, yes, I apologize.
The Chairman and my teacher said
I couldn't accompany them,
which is quite unfortunate, if you ask me.
Oh, of course, by "spending time with him"
I don't mean that he and I--
Argh! What is the condition?
You have to take down Knuckle and Shoot.
It's unthinkable, really.
How dare those vulgar, rude,
barbaric brats go to the NGL before me?
[Gon] So she's an enhancer like me.
I don't like this.
Hold on. Knuckle and Shoot?
So you're not here to fight us?
-That's right.
-[boys gasp]
After all, I am not the one who's been
assigned to defeating Knuckle and Shoot.
That job belongs to you.
They too received a condition.
We only have one month's time.
Okay, we were told to keep these tiles
in our possession for a month.
So you can bet that in that time
someone's gonna come for them.
And I'm a Beast Hunter!
Extermination Team candidates,
I challenge you to a duel.
So come and fight me, okay?
[man 1] Where?
[man 2] What location?
[man 3] You have to tell them
where to find you.
Bring it on. Hear me?
You won't get away from me.
[Killua] I wouldn't go
even if he said where.
[Killua] He's just a decoy.
His partner's probably hiding somewhere.
You know, I'm even willing to bet
that they're watching to see
if anyone reacts suspiciously
before they make a move.
And according to Palm,
they don't even know our names.
-So we're in the clear.
-Mmm-hmm.
They were just trying
to lure us out somehow.
Only an idiot
would pull a stunt like that.
[Gon] What's it gonna take to defeat him?
Also, according to that guy,
I'm not qualified to judge
if a fight can be won.
But I disagree.
If you want to survive,
you have to increase your odds of victory.
If you're fighting someone you can only
beat once or twice out of a hundred times,
-don't bother.
-[gasps]
You want 50-50 at least.
70% or better if it's at all possible.
And for us to get to that point,
there are still two things we have to do.
We need to work on
all our fundamental skills
-and learn about our opponent's abilities.
-[grunts]
[Gon] Hmm.
Half of me agrees with you
and half doesn't.
What does that mean?
I agree that we should work on
our fundamentals.
I just don't agree we need to know
exactly what their abilities are.
Really? Why the hell not?
Come on, why add to all the risks
without any real benefits?
I know, but once we're inside,
that is what we're going to be facing.
[gasps]
Our goal isn't to defeat
Knuckle and Shoot, it's to get stronger.
Strong enough to go back to the NGL
and rescue Kite.
I mean, we've got to be powerful enough to
beat enemies we don't know anything about
at a moment's notice.
[both gasp] You two know each other?
[Palm] No, I just did
a little research on you.
Okay, but we only know her from…
We must plot to kill
Mr. Morel's disciples.
[boys] No, thanks.
-[Biscuit] Now let's get started.
-[boys] Osu!
[grunts]
That hurt! What was that for?
[Gon] But you don't understand.
We have to get back there
as soon as possible so we can save Kite.
Wait, what are you talking about?
[Neferpitou] That was so much fun.
I'd love to do it again.
With you.
[Biscuit] I see.
What if you make
those same mistakes again?
[Killua] At her age, no wonder
she's a pro at chewing people out.
Show me Ren.
Killua, how long can you go?
On a really good day,
I can do just about 55 minutes max.
Do that,
and then we can move on to the next step.
Train like your lives depend on it.
[laughs]
[grunts]
[groans, pants]
[Biscuit] Oh, come on,
you didn't even last an hour.
Okay, now keep going.
[both straining]
They say it should take about a month
to prolong your Ren by a mere 10 minutes.
[dog whimpers]
Damn them!
Those damn bastards didn't even show up!
You cowards deserve to die!
[barks]
So where the hell's your owner?
You gotta pick up after your dogs.
Keep our parks clean, damn it.
And from the looks of it, now would
be the perfect time to use my ability.
Hmm.
[piano playing]
[Biscuit] Magical Spa Services.
Peachy relief. Piano massage.
[Gon sighs]
[sighs]
-[Palm] Excuse me.
-Huh?
I do hope I'm not rude for saying this,
but I'll let you choose how to train them.
My ability selected you
is the answer I seek, after all.
However, if after a month
we determine it would be impossible
for them to defeat Morel's pupils,
I sincerely doubt that
I would be able to restrain myself.
I must go to the NGL.
I want to go right now, in fact.
and then I don't get to go,
then I may end up killing you all.
Therefore, if you don't think
they stand a chance,
you should give up sooner
rather than later.
My anger won't be as terrible then,
judging by my past experiences.
I'm really not the one
you should be telling that to.
You can tell the two of them
when they're awake, okay?
[grunts]
[Palm gasps]
That's how he is. Just have faith in him.
[grunting]
-[shuddering] Oh, dear! Oh, gosh! Oh, no!
-[Biscuit] Hmm.
Anyway, at the moment, I'm far more
concerned about the guys back in the NGL.
What exactly does the Chairman
plan to do for the next month? Hey.
Uh… Oh, they said
they were going to scout and whittle,
The experts can't come to a consensus
on how much time remains
between now and when the king is born.
The Chairman is acting on the assumption
that the earliest it will be
is in two months.
This isn't good.
That thing looks a lot stronger than me.
[Knov] Stronger than you, Chairman?
Surely you jest.
And although I'm flattered, I'm currently
just about even with the two of you.
Then you're more than
strong enough, Chairman.
You should be more confident.
[scoffs] Always ready with a comeback.
But we've still gotta fight them.
I would prefer to avoid that eventuality.
A non-violent solution
would be a much better outcome.
Our target is the Queen,
and the Queen alone.
But it will be quite difficult
to slip through his En surveillance.
There is no way to avoid confrontation.
The only question is
how we'll manage to win.
If you have any ideas,
I'd be glad to hear them.
[scoffs] You love to tease, don't you?
You already knew what you would do
when you chose the two of us, didn't you?
We go and exterminate the Ants silently
one at a time.
Now let's take it slow, all right?
Now, go.
I guess you have a point there.
It's possible that they're decoys.
Hey, wait a sec.
Was I just speaking out loud?
[Neferpitou] Meow I get it.
So you're Shaiapouf.
Well, a mere observation.
So you can read my thoughts, can't you?
I'm not sure I like it.
I can understand the sentiment.
[chuckles softly]
But soon, [giggles] he'll awaken.
That's wonderful news.
'Cause, you see,
I still haven't made a final decision
about exactly
what ability I should develop.
Oh, yeah, it's so simple.
All I need to do is fix him.
[laughing]
No way.
We'll never give up.
[closing theme music playing]
[upbeat music playing]
[Gon] Next time, Duel and Escape.
It's on, Killua.
[Killua] It's on, Gon!
[both yell] Janken rock!
[Gon] I lost.
[singer singing in Japanese]